Kingdom of Liones
Outskirts of the Imperial City
≫(老騎士)おい！
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)ひっ！
You over there!
Are you free?
(老騎士)手 空いてっか？
ちょっくら手伝ってくれや｡
I need some help over here.
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)は… はい｡
Yes!
(老騎士)どっから来た？
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)ｹｲﾝｽﾞです｡
Where are you from?
Kaynes.
Kaynes?
(老騎士)ケインズ？
おりゃ 王国に
４０年仕えた➡
I've served this kingdom for 40 years,
but not once have I heard of that place.
ロートルだが
聞いたことねぇな｡
Well, it's a really small rural village.
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)そりゃあもう
田舎も田舎ですから｡
その様子じゃ
聖騎士見習いにも
なってねぇな｡
Looking at you, you've yet to become
an apprentice of the Holy Knights, no?
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)ははっ…
聖騎士なんて 俺にはとても…｡
The Holy Knights? No, I'm just...
(老騎士)
なんて言ってるヤツには
ちときついかもな｡
What comes next might be
a bit hard for guys like you.
これは…｡
What is this?
They're all Holy Knights.
(老騎士)
全部 聖騎士さ｡
Wh-What the hell happened here?
な… 何があったんです？
(老騎士)｢何が｣？
"What?" you ask?
ぶっ殺されたのよ｡➡
They were all slaughtered.
It happened all in an instant too.
それも 一瞬のうちにな｡
あぁ…｡
By just seven people.
(老騎士)たった七人に｡
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale between humans
and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
The Holy Knights who protected this country
＜国を守る聖騎士たちは
絶大なる魔力を有し➡
used immensely powerful magic.
They were both feared and revered.
恐れ 敬われた＞
However,
＜ だが その中で 国を裏切り➡
there was a group who betrayed their country and turned their blades toward the remaining Knights.
全聖騎士を
敵に回した者たちがいた＞
＜人々は
彼らを 七つの大罪と呼んだ＞
To the masses, they were known as the "Seven Deadly Sins."
10 Years Later
Near Kaynes Village
Episode 1
The Seven Deadly Sins
(客)いや～！
(客)はははっ｡
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)ほいよ！
大ジョッキ５つ お待ちどおっ！
There ya go! 5 giant steins of beer!
Is there room for any more?
(客)まだ入れるかい？
ここ どうぞ！
Right here is fine!
Sorry, but do you mind if they sit here?
悪ぃな
ちょっと詰めてくれる？ よっと｡
ちっこいのに
よく働く店員さんだぜ｡
He really works hard as a waiter for being so small.
I'm the owner of this place, not a waiter.
店員じゃなくて マスター｡
ここ 俺の店だから｡
It is my bar, after all.
マ… マスター？ あんな子供が？
That kid's the owner?
Here you go. It's finally done!
ほ～ら 焼き上がったよ｡
A Boar Hat's special meat pie!
｢豚の帽子｣亭 特製ミートパイだ｡
おおっ うまそ～！
It looks delicious!
Let's dig in!
(３人)いっただっきま～す！
(３人)まっず～～！
Disgusting!
I knew it.
やっぱり｡
酒はうまいが 料理はまずいって➡
I guess my bar's known more for
its alcohol than its food, after all.
評判なんだよな うち｡
(３人)それを先に言え！
Why didn't you say that first?!
Are you tryin' to pick a fight with us, kid?
なめてんのか!? このガキ！
Hey, wait, he's got a sword on him.
おい こいつ 剣持ってるぞ｡
Good grief.
やれやれ 困ったお客さんだな｡
What troublesome guests we got here.
パチン
片づけろ｡
Clean it up.
Geez, what a waste of time.
(ﾎｰｸ)ったく… たりぃな｡
俺に なんの用だよ？
What do you want from me?
ぶ… 豚がしゃべってる！
The pig is talking!
Don't all of you get surprised now.
いちいち驚くなよ｡
これだから 田舎者は｡
This is why I hate country bumpkins.
ホーク 床掃除 頼む｡
Hawk, can you clean up the floor for me?
ちっ！ めんどくせぇ｡
What a pain.
Having to deal with eating
leftovers isn't exactly fun, you know.
残飯処理係も楽じゃねぇぜ｡
Honestly, how about making something good for once?
ったく もうちっと
マシな残飯 食わせろよな｡
豚の丸焼きなら もうちっと
マシに作れそうな気がするな｡
I guess if I were to make a pig roast, it would taste pretty damn good.
んまぁ～い！ ここの残飯 最高！
Delicious! The leftovers here are amazing!
(一同)はははっ｡
≫バン！(ﾄﾞｱの音)
はぁ はぁ…｡ でっ でた！➡
I-It's real!
I'm not joking! I saw him with my own eyes.
ほんとだって！
この目で見たんだよ｡
ありゃあ 間違いなく
さまよう錆の騎士だって｡
I'm absolutely sure of it.
It's the Wandering Rust Knight.
It's a rumor that's been floating around recently.
最近 噂になってんな｡
いるはずねぇだろ｡ んなもん
子供を叱るときの方便だろうが｡
There's no way something like that exists.
It's just something we make up to scare the children.
"Don't tell so many lies.
あんまり悪さしてると
血で錆びた鎧を着た➡
If you do, the blood-rusted knight of the
Seven Deadly Sins will come get you," right?
七つの大罪が出るぞ～ってな｡
(２人)ははははっ｡
The Seven Deadly Sins?
七つの大罪？
おう｡
Yeah.
The young owner here doesn't know the story?
若いマスターさんだと
もう知らねぇか｡
You even have a poster of them. You know, that one over there.
手配書があるじゃねぇか｡
あれだ あれだ｡
It was 10 years ago, right?
(客)１０年前だっけ？➡
When many of the Holy Knights that gathered from all over the kingdom lost their lives.
王国全土から集められた
聖騎士様が➡
何十人も殺されたって
大事件があってな｡➡
It was a huge ordeal.
Those are the murderers there.
その犯人が
こいつら 七つの大罪よ｡
They're known as the "Seven Deadly Sins."
The Great Holy Knight was murdered so brutally
(客)聖騎士長様にいたっては➡
あまりに むごい殺され方で➡
that you could barely recognize him anymore.
見れた姿じゃなかったって
いうじゃねぇか｡
Their captain, Meliodas,
was the worst of the bunch.
(客)団長のメリオダスってのが
また恐ろしいヤツでな｡➡
There's a rumor that he destroyed
part of the country single-handedly.
国一個 滅ぼしたって話も
あるくれぇだ｡
They still haven't been caught yet, have they?
(客)こいつらって
まだ捕まってないんだろ？
Yeah, not a single one of them.
(客)ああ｡ 一人たりともな｡
Some rumor is going around
that they've died already, though.
(客)一部じゃ
全員死んだって噂もあるけど｡
There's no way they're dead.
(客)死んでるね それ絶対｡➡
今の聖騎士様たちが
許すわけないよ｡
The Holy Knights wouldn't have just let them go.
Yeah, that's true.
(客)ああ～ 確かに｡
王様が 病で倒れちまった今も➡
Even though the king passed away due to an illness,
Here you go.
the Holy Knights are doing a pretty good job protecting the kingdom.
聖騎士様たちが しっかりと
国を守ってくれてんだもんな｡
でも この手配書
毎年 更新されてるぜ？
But these wanted posters are renewed every year.
やっぱ まだ
死んでねぇってことじゃねぇのか？
Maybe there's a chance they're still alive.
Even if they are,
つっても 錆びた鎧の騎士が
歩いてるってのは➡
it's a bit of a stretch to say there's a knight in
rusty armor wandering around, don't you think?
いくらなんでも…｡ なあ？
はははっ ないない｡
Yeah, you're right.
≫ガシャン(足音)
あっ｡
ガシャン ガシャン ガシャン…
プゴッ プゴップゴッ｡
なんだ？ この錆臭ぇ臭いは｡
What's with this rusty smell?
The... Seven...
(錆の騎士)な… なつの…➡
たい… ざ… い…｡
Deadly... Sins.
He's here!
(一同)でたぁ～～‼
(客)ひぃ～！
(客)七つの大罪だ～！
He really came!
お前 誰だ？
Who are you?
この子が 七つの大罪？
Is this really one of the Seven Deadly Sins?
It's a woman!
女の子… だぜ｡
うんにゃ｡
えっ!?
This sleeping face.
この寝顔 このボディーライン➡
This body line.
This smell.
この匂い➡
And this elasticity....
この弾力…｡
やっぱり 女だな｡
見りゃ分かんだろ！
It's definitely a woman.
You can tell just from looking!
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)あ… あの？
U-Um...
動悸にも異常なし！
あ… ありがとうございます？
Nothing out of the ordinary here.
Th-Thank you very much.
ここは？ あの… 私はなぜ？
Where am I?
Um...
Why am I...
You came into the bar in a daze and suddenly fainted.
ふら～っと店に入ってきて➡
いきなり ぶっ倒れたんだ お前｡
Bar?
店？
｢豚の帽子｣亭｡ 俺の店だ｡
It's called "Boar Hat." It's my bar.
So you're the owner?
あなたが マスターさん？
おかしいか？
Is that strange?
いっ いえ！ その…
背中の剣が見えたものですから｡
N-No.
I saw the sword on your back, so...
ああ～ これか｡
Oh, this thing?
きゃあ！ あっ…｡
へへ～！ ビビった？
柄だけでも ちらつかせてりゃ➡
Sorry. Did I scare ya?
Even if it's just the hilt,
it still looks pretty authentic, right?
それなりに見えんだろ？
これぞ
食い逃げへの抑止力ってやつだ｡
I guess you can call it a deterrent for people to eat and run.
おめぇの飯を食わされたあげくに➡
I feel worse for the customers
who actually pay to eat your food.
金 ふんだくられる
客の方が 気の毒だ｡
うわぁ～！ しゃべる豚さんだ！
It's a talking pig!
ホークだぜ｡ よろしくな｡
I'm Hawk. Nice to meet you.
I asked my father for one as a birthday present before.
この前
父上に 誕生日プレゼントに➡
おねだりしたんです｡
で その豚 もらったのか？
Did he end up getting you one?
あっ いえ…｡
No...
Oh, that reminds me.
そだ｡ 腹減ってないか？
よけりゃ食わしてやるよ｡
Are you hungry?
If you'd like, you can have some.
ポークちゃんを？
ポークじゃねぇ！ ホーク！
Of Pork here?
My name is Hawk, not Pork!
It's ready!
≪出来たぞ｡
あっ｡
In addition to taking me in,
you're also feeding me.
介抱していただいたうえに
食事まで…｡
I don't know how I can possibly repay you.
なんて お礼を言えばいいか｡
Give it a try before you say that.
礼言う前に まず食ってみな｡
はい｡ いただきます｡
Okay.
Thanks for the food.
どうだ？ まずいだろ？
Well?
It's bad, right?
あっ はい…｡
(２人)やっぱり｡
Y-Yes...
I knew it.
あっ｡
でも➡
But...
It's very... good.
すごく… おいしい｡
なあ お前
あんな鎧姿で 何してたんだ？
By the way, what were you doing in that suit of armor?
I'm searching for the Seven Deadly Sins.
捜してるんです 七つの大罪を｡
Them again? You don't even know if they're alive or not.
なんでまた？
生きてるか死んでるかも➡
分かんねぇような連中だぜ？
大悪党だぜ？
Not to mention they're dangerous.
≫ドンドンドン！(扉をたたく音)
≫(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)開けろ！➡
Open up!
村人からの通告があった！➡
We've got a tip from one of the villagers.
We are the knights stationed at the base of this mountain.
我々は 麓に駐留する➡
聖騎士様配下の
｢山猫の髭｣騎士団｡➡
We serve the Great Holy Knight himself.
七つの大罪とおぼしき錆の騎士を
捕らえに来た！➡
We're here to capture the Rust Knight as a lead to the Seven Deadly Sins.
≪おとなしく出てこい！
Come out peacefully!
なんか うるせぇヤツが来たぜ｡
聖騎士…｡
We've got some pretty noisy guys out there.
Holy Knights...
出てきませんね｡
それにしても➡
Looks like they're not coming out.
Aside from that...
Since when has there been a bar on top of this hill?
こんな丘の上に
酒場なんて いつ建ったんだ？
(団員)そういや
３日前に通ったときには➡
Now that you mention it, I was here
three days ago and the hill was desolate.
何もなかったような…｡
Don't let your guard down.
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)油断するな｡
相手は １０年前とはいえ➡
It might've been 10 years ago,
but he's still one of the Seven Deadly Sins.
元王直属の聖騎士だぞ｡
There's no need to worry, Alioni.
He's probably an old man by now.
心配ありませんよ
アリオーニさん｡➡
所詮はロートル｡
(団員)そうそう｡➡
He's right.
We were trained by Lord Twigo, so he'll be no match for us.
ツイーゴ様のもとで鍛えられてる
我らの敵じゃありませんよ｡
Don't take them lightly.
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)
ヤツらを侮るな｡ 前にも話したろ｡
Don't make me repeat myself.
During that incident 10 years ago,
１０年前の あの騒動のとき➡
dozens of Holy Knights were killed in an instant.
何十人もの聖騎士が
一瞬のうちに…｡
About that...
それもなぁ…｡
なんだ？
What?
Well, isn't that a bit of an exaggeration?
いや その… ちょっと
大げさなんじゃないかなと｡
はあ？ どういうことだ？
１人いりゃ➡
Huh?
What do you mean?
If one Holy Knight is as strong as a country,
there's no way dozens of them were killed, right?
一国の兵力にも値する
なんて言われてる聖騎士が➡
そんな何十人も…｡ なあ？
I saw it with my own eyes!
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)
俺は この目で見たんだよ！
(団員)まあ まあ｡
ひとまず アリオーニさんは➡
All right, all right. But please stand down this time, Alioni.
下がっててください｡ ここは
俺たちで なんとかしますんで｡
Leave this one to us.
おい 出てこ～い！
Hey, get your ass out here!
You called?
呼んだか？
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)なんだ 貴様は!?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the owner of this bar.
俺は この店のマスターだ｡
Where's the Rust Knight?
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)錆の騎士は どこにいる？
そいつを出せ｡
Bring him out!
ふぅ… 出てこいよ｡
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)ん？
Come out!
へへへっ｡ 俺を呼んだか？
Were you looking for me?
The Rust Knight, Hawk?
この錆の騎士 ホークを！
こ… この豚が七つの大罪ですか!?
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)んなわけないだろ！
Th-This pig is one of the Seven Deadly Sins?!
Of course he isn't!
Wh-Wh-What was that?!
ななな… なんと！
俺は 残飯処理騎士団➡
I'll have you know that I'm the leader of
the knights in charge of leftover disposal!
団長なんだぜ｡
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)んな騎士団があるか！
There is no such group of knights!
この豚でよければ
煮るなり焼くなり➡
If this pig is who you're after,
please feel free to do as you plea—
好きに…｡
どっちも勘弁しろ！
Like hell they can!
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)
ガキ… 騎士を愚弄するとは➡
You brat!
You've got some guts to mock us knights!
いい度胸だな｡
あっ！ アリオーニさん
裏から 女が逃げました！
Alioni, a woman is escaping out the back!
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)何!?
急ぎ ツイーゴ様に伝えろ！➡
What?!
Tell Lord Twigo immediately!
She's most likely the Rust Knight!
おそらく
その女が錆の騎士だ｡ 追え！
Get going!
(一同)おお～！
(団員)待て～！
Yes!
Stop right there!
ブヒッ｡
You bitch!
≫(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)捕らえろ～！
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)七つの大罪の一人を
追い込んだとあらば 相当な手柄｡
If she really is one of the Seven Deadly Sins, she must possess some incredible power.
If that's true, I can finally become a Holy Knight!
そうなれば
俺も いよいよ聖騎士見習いに…｡
(団員)うわっ！
な… なんだ!? どうした!?
H-Huh? What's wrong?
ぶ… 豚が突進してきます！
おらおらおら… おら～！
Th-The pig is charging at us!
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)
おわぁ～！ 来るな 来るな！
No, don't come near me. Stay away!
来るな～！ ん？➡
うわっ… くっ！ えっ いない？
She's gone?!
Take this!
あらよっと！
うわっ！ ああ～～～‼
てめぇらに恨みはねぇが
これで 今晩の飯の量２倍｡
I've got nothing against you guys, but I'm gonna get double the dinner tonight for this!
あの… 二度も助けていただいて➡
Um...
You saved me for the second time...
なんとお礼を言えばいいか…｡
I really don't know how I can ever repay you.
You know, you can totally hit him if you want.
だから ねえちゃん
そいつ 殴っていいって｡
で お前は なんで
七つの大罪を捜してるんだ？
So...
Why are ya searching for the Seven Deadly Sins?
To stop...
聖騎士たちを止めるためです｡
the Holy Knights.
Why do you want to stop the Holy Knights?
聖騎士を止めるって
何から？
The Holy Knights are the ones
protecting the Kingdom of Liones.
聖騎士っていや
このリオネスを守る➡
騎士の中の騎士 英雄だろうが｡
They're heroes, aren't they?
でも その彼らが この国に➡
Yes, but...
What if they were to bring war to this kingdom?
戦をもたらそうとしていたら？
プゴッ？
先日 聖騎士たちの手により➡
A few days ago,
the Holy Knights captured the king and the rest of the royal family and confined them one by one.
国王以下 王族の者たちが
次々と拘束されました｡
国王は
病気でふせってんじゃねぇのか？
I thought the king died of an illness?
それは
聖騎士たちが流したデマです｡
That's just a lie made up by the Holy Knights.
I don't know why they would choose to start a war.
彼らが なんのために
戦を始めるつもりなのか➡
分かりません｡ ただ➡
But...
They've begun recruiting people from the towns and villages around the kingdom,
王国と周辺の町や村から
人々を強制的に集めては➡
steadily preparing for war.
着々と その準備を進めています｡
じきに この辺りにも
影響が及んでくるでしょう｡
I'm sure the effects of their actions will reach this area soon as well.
マジかよ｡
大変だなぁ｡
Seriously?
That sounds pretty bad.
How are you always so calm?
って…
のんきだな おめぇは相変わらず｡
So how do the Seven Deadly Sins tie in with all of this?
でもさ それと
七つの大罪と どうつながんだ？
唯一 聖騎士たちを
止める希望があるとすれば➡
The only hope we have of
stopping the Holy Knights' plan is
七つの大罪だけなんです！
with the help of the Seven Deadly Sins!
お前さ
七つの大罪が どんな連中か➡
Come on,
you're searching for them despite
knowing full well what they're like?
知ってて捜してんの？
七つの大罪…｡
The Seven Deadly Sins...
七匹の獣の印を体に刻んだ➡
They were originally seven brutal criminals
who had the mark of seven
beasts carved into their bodies.
七人の
凶悪な大罪人から結成された➡
They were known as the
strongest and cruelest knights.
王国最強最悪の騎士団｡
And 10 years ago,
彼らは 今から１０年前
王国転覆を謀った疑いで➡
they attempted to overthrow the throne.
王国全聖騎士から総攻撃を受け
ちりぢりになった｡
However, the Holy Knights
launched a grand offensive at them,
and they vanished from this world.
んで 全員死んだって噂も
あったっけなぁ｡
And then there's the rumor that they were all killed.
There's no way those people were killed off that easily!
そんなすごい人たちが
簡単に死ぬわけがありません！
んん～ でも 大罪人なんだろ？
They were criminals, though.
The ones making people suffer
right now are the Holy Knights!
現実に 人々を苦しめているのは
聖騎士たちなんです！
昔…
まだ 私が５つか６つのころ➡
In the past, when I was just five or six,
父が よく話してくれました｡
my father used to tell me about them.
Although they were the Seven
Deadly Sins, they were still the best!
彼らは…
七つの大罪こそが最高の…｡
ザシュ！
ん？
ドドーン！
ああっ！
きゃあ～！
勘弁しろ～！
Give me a break!
Whoops.
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)おっと…
通告にあった人間かどうか➡
I forgot to confirm whether they
were the people in the report or not.
確かめるのを忘れておった｡➡
Confirmed.
決定！ 身元不明者２名死亡｡
Two unknown people dead.
ってことでいいかの｡
Is that all right?
B-But Alioni was beneath that cliff!
しっ しかし
崖下に アリオーニさんが…｡
Then we'll just report that three people died.
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ならば
３名死亡にしておけばよい｡
そっ そんな！
ツイーゴ様 それは あんまりです｡
That's—
Lord Twigo, that's terrible!
Well, how about I make it seven people, then?
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ならば ７名死亡か？
Anything but that!
(団員)それだけは お許しを…｡
(団員)あっ！
よっと｡
(団員)ア… アリオーニさん！
Alioni!
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)お前たち
何を勝手に生きておる！➡
What're you lot doing alive?!
わしの死亡決定を
変更するでないわ！
Don't just go and change my
confirmed death toll like that!
勝手に決定すんな～！
Don't confirm it so easily then!
おい 起きてるか？
あっ はい｡
Hey, are you awake?
Oh! Yes!
よし 俺が合図したら
森に向かって走れ｡
All right.
When I give the signal, run to the forest.
いいな？
は… はい｡
Got it?
Y-Yes.
So, which of you is the supposed
member of the Seven Deadly Sins?
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)して どちらが七つの大罪と
おぼしき人物なんじゃ？➡
Neither of you resemble the ones in the posters, but...
どちらも
手配書とは似とらんようじゃが｡
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ん!? ほう～｡➡
これは わしも運がいい｡➡
It seems I'm in luck.
That symbol on your earring
means you're from the royal family.
その耳飾りの紋章は
王家のものだ｡➡
つまり 御身は➡
That means you're...
Confirmed! You're Princess Elizabeth!
決定！ エリザベス王女！
あっ！
エリザベス… 王女？
Princess Elizabeth?
エリザベス王女っつったら
この国の第三王女様じゃねぇか！
Princess Elizabeth?!
As in the third princess of this kingdom?!
There's a search order out for you throughout the kingdom.
御身には 王国から
捜索指令が出ておりましてな｡
生きたまま捕らえよとの
ご命令ではありますが➡
The orders are to capture you alive, but...
It can't be helped if you die in an
accident on the battlefield, can it?
事故死ならば
致し方ないでしょうな｡
We're leaving!
走れ！
プゴッ プゴッ プゴッ！
Got it!
There's no way I can allow
myself to get captured now!
私は まだ捕まるわけには…
諦めるわけにはいきません！
I can't just give up now!
おお～！ 決定！➡
Confirmed! Accidental death!
事故死～！
あっ！
ドォーン！
うぅ… あっ！
よう｡
Yo!
ホークも無事… みたいだな｡
It seems you're fine too, from the looks of it.
この豚串状態が無事だと？
You call this skewered-pig state "fine"?!
うわぁ～ん！ おっ母～！
Mom!
豚？ まあいい｡
A pig? Well, no matter.
エリザベス｡
おい どこ行くんだよ？
Elizabeth...
Hey, where are you going?
逃げきれません｡
I won't be able to escape.
お前 諦めるわけにはいかねぇって
言ってただろ｡
You...
Didn't you say that you'd never give up?
私が おとなしく投降すれば➡
If I surrender to him quietly,
あなたの命を
むやみには奪わないはずです｡
there's no reason for him to take your life as well.
ザシュ！
あっ！
お願い…
あなただけでも逃げてください！
I beg you!
At the very least, you should make it out of here alive!
どのみち
ありゃあ 俺たち両方 殺す気だぞ｡
It looks like he'll kill us either way.
どうして…｡
Why are you...
I was so happy...
私 うれしかったんです｡
たった一人で
七つの大罪を捜す旅に出て➡
I went to search for the Seven Deadly Sins all on my own.
旅なんてしたことなくって
すごく不安で…｡
I've never been on a journey until now.
I was so worried.
In order to hide my identity, I wore armor
I wasn't used to and walked until I was exhausted.
正体がバレないよう
着慣れない鎧で➡
くたくたになるまで歩いて｡
けど
誰を頼ることもできなくて…｡
And I wasn't able to rely on anyone...
なのに… あなたは➡
But you...
Someone who didn't even know who I was...
どこの誰とも知れない私に
優しくしてくれて｡
treated me so kindly.
That's why I don't want to
get you involved any further.
だから
私は 名も知らないあなたを➡
これ以上 巻き込みたくないの！
You, whose name I don't even know!
メリオダス それが俺の名前だ｡
えっ？
Meliodas. That's my name.
まさか…｡
It can't be.
That's...
そんな…｡
へへっ｡
But you look like...
あなたは だって…｡
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)くっ… あいつは どこだ!?
(団員)アリオーニさん｡
Where's he at?!
Alioni!
あの 剣を背負ったヤツだ！
(団員)落ち着いてください➡
Where's the guy with the sword?!
Please calm down, Alioni!
アリオーニさん｡
今 ツイーゴ様が追い込んで…｡
Lord Twigo is chasing them right now.
バカ！
あいつを怒らせちゃダメだ！➡
Idiot! It'll be bad if he enrages him!
国が滅ぶぞ！
えっ？
The country will be destroyed!
When he saved me,
(ｱﾘｵｰﾆ)
助け出されたとき 見たんだよ｡➡
I saw it!
あいつは本物だ…｡
いちばんやばいヤツなんだよ！
He's the real deal—the most dangerous of them all.
あいつの肩の印 あれは…｡
The symbol on his shoulder...
That symbol is one of the beasts—
その印は 獣の… いえ➡
No.
The dragon...
龍の！
ふん！
ドォン！
ん？ ぐおっ！➡
どういうことだ？
What's the meaning of this?
My sword should've hit you.
わしの剣は
確実に こやつをしとめた｡
だが 一撃をもらったのは
このわしじゃと!?
But the one getting hit instead
is me?!
What is that?!
なんだ それは!?➡
A sword with a broken blade?!
刃折れの剣!?
Meliodas,
メリオダス…
あなたは本当に あの…｡
are you really...
Wait...
待てよ？ 貴様の顔には見覚えが｡
I remember seeing your face before.
But how can this be?!
いや… だとしたら なぜ➡
昔と 姿が変わっていない!?
You haven't changed a bit since then!
俺が誰だか 分かったか？
So you've finally realized who I am.
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ま… まさか！
I-It can't be!
Is it really you?!
本当に貴様は～～‼
キン！
ドォン！
け… 決定…｡
C-Confirmed.
This immeasurable power...
この尋常ならざる力は➡
あの伝説の…｡
The legendary...
ドオォォーン！
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ぎゃあ～～‼
七つの大罪 憤怒の罪➡
The Seven Deadly Sins, Wrath of the Dragon.
憤怒の罪 メリオダス！
Dragon's Wrath, Meliodas!
The Seven Deadly Sins
<
Dragon's Wrath
Meliodas
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
I run through my unwavering thoughts
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume ni tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
I run through my emotions of giving up
akirameru omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume ni tsunai da kimi to
With that, it looks like you've
found your first one, Elizabeth.
これで
一人目が見つかったわけだな➡
エリザベス｡
えっ？
残りの六人のことなんだけどさ
俺も 用があって➡
As for the remaining six...
I've business with them, so I'm also trying to figure out where they are.
最近 あいつら 捜しはじめたんだ｡
情報集めのために
酒場をやりながらな｡
I've been running a bar for the sake of gathering information.
これで 看板娘がいてくれたら
客も情報も もっと集まるんだがな｡
If I had a girl serving at the bar,
I think I'd be able to get even more.
一緒に行くだろ？
You'll come with me, right?
はい！
Yes!
(団員)ツイーゴ様 しっかり！
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)うぅ…｡
Lord Twigo, snap out of it!
お… 王国に増援要請を…｡
R-Request for reinforcements from the kingdom!
This is serious!
これは… いっ 一大事だぞ｡
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴ～～ッ！
ん？
ズドーーン！
(ﾂｲｰｺﾞ)ぐわぁ～！
ナイスタイミングだろ！
Nice timing!
As expected from Hawk's momma!
さっすが ホークママ｡
呼びに行ったのは俺だ！
I'm the one who jumped here!
Let's get going to the next town!
さあ 行くぞ 次の町へ｡
出発だ ホークママ！
Let's go, Hawk's momma!
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴ～～ッ！
きゃあ～～‼
＜ この出会いは 偶然か必然か＞
Was this meeting coincidence or fate?
＜待ち受けるものは
絶望か希望か＞
Is it hope or despair that awaits us?
＜ こうして 七つの大罪を捜す➡
And thus, my adventures with Meliodas in
search of the remaining Seven Deadly Sins began.
私とメリオダス様の冒険が
始まったのです＞
Approximately 38 Miles East of Kaynes Village
Fort Solgales
The Seven Deadly Sins...
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)七つの大罪｡
うっ…｡
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)
今度こそ 本物であればな｡
I guess it's the real deal this time.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)１０年も待ちわびたのだ
七つの大罪を滅ぼす日を｡
I waited 10 years for this day...
The day that I would destroy the Seven Deadly Sins.
＜七つの大罪を捜す
メリオダスたちの旅に➡
新たな仲間が加わった｡
その名は エリザベス＞
エリザベスです｡ 不束者ですが
よろしくお願いします｡
Next Episode's Report
おう よろしくな｡
ところで 不束者って➡
During Melioda's search for the Seven Deadly Sins,
どういう意味か知ってる？
えっ？ し… 知りません｡
a new member has joined!
Her name is Elizabeth!
俺もだ｡ じゃあ またな！
I'm Elizabeth.
I might be inexperienced, but I hope we get along!
＜冒険の旅は まだまだ続く＞
次回 ｢七つの大罪｣｡
｢聖騎士の剣｣｡
Nice to meet you!
By the way, do you know what "inexperienced" really means?
ちなみに
太くて丈夫って意味だぜ｡
N-No, I don't.
ほ… 本当ですか？
大型で強い台風１８号は
Neither do I!
See you next time!
Their adventures shall continue!
九州南部を暴風域に巻き込みなが
ら北上している｡
Next time on "The Seven Deadly Sins":
Excalibur.
今夜遅く､四国に接近し
By the way, being big means you're healthy!
明日にかけては本州に接近､
Episode 2
The Excalibur
Really?
または上陸するおそれがある｡
See you
next week!